Wow, why can't you get it?
That's so cute!
It's like petting a dog.
People don't really talk when they eat crab.
Do you know that?
Hello! I'm Ayaka Takamoto from Hyugaizaka46!
Today I'd like to introduce you to my newest daily makeup for the year 2023!
Yay!
Since I started my YouTube channel, I've been getting so many requests from the sun to watch my makeup videos.
I've been getting a lot of ear rattling and other things, so this will be the video I've been longing for! Yay!
Let's get started!
Well, let's get started!
By the way, I'm really wearing no makeup right now!
I'm so embarrassed! I really don't want you to look at it.
I'll try to complete it as soon as possible.
First of all, I'd like to start with the base makeup.
Base makeup, this is a primer.
This is Lior Skin Forever Glow Veil!
First of all, I'm going to use this all over the skin.
I'm going to take this much.
I'm so embarrassed!
Please don't be embarrassed, I don't look so bad even without makeup!
It's very moisturizing.
It's also very resistant to smudging.
It's totally fine even in the summer.
It spreads very well and is easy to spread.
I'm done, so
So, I use a sponge like this.
I used to be very particular about sponges.
But now, I don't know, I don't care about anything.
I use this to blend it a little bit.
If I just use my hands, it doesn't adhere well.
If you just use your hands, it doesn't adhere well.
So if you use a sponge to hold it down a little bit, the makeup will last longer.
Will the makeup last? Will it last long?
Well, it's not.Hmmm... No, it's not.
It doesn't fall apart easily.
Croncealer here.
It's No. 01 of Sume Decorte's To Perfect Palette.
I put this between the primer and the concealer.
This color? It's a little bit orange.
First, hide the dark circles.
This is very important.
I think dark circles are the most common problem area.
How do I make them blend well?
It's really difficult to completely erase them.
But with this method
I think it covers them well. It's about right.
Here, yes, I'm going to put orange.
Then, dab it on with a sponge.
Ding, dong, dong.
Okay, now we're going to use a foundation.
I'm going to use the light beige cushion foundation from &B.
This is so good, it doesn't fall apart at all.
It goes really well with any foundation.
I think cushion foundations are often sticky with sponges and puffs like this.
I think cushion foundation often comes out sticky.
But with this one, I don't have to put too much pressure on it.
It's like brushing your teeth.
I think it takes 200g of toothpaste.
I think 200 is too much.
About 100.
Then try to press down with about 100 grams of force.
Is it clean?
I think it looked like I was tapping a lot.
Surprisingly, it doesn't look too thick.
Then go back to the concealer.
I'm going to use the color that's gone the most.
I'm going to remove dark circles and around the nose again.
It's impossible to erase all of them.
It's impossible to erase everything, so I think it's important to do it with the hope that it will disappear as much as possible.I think it's important to try to make it disappear as much as possible.
If you get too obsessive about it, you'll become very attached to it and it will become a complex.
You'll end up feeling depressed every time you look in the mirror.
Let's do it with the feeling that it would be nice if the presence disappears.
The area around the nose is also prone to redness.
Also, let's raise this wide-angle angle.
I'm going to dab it on with the sponge again.
Next, I'm going to apply the powder. Here is the powder I'm using.
I'm using Nars Soft Matte Advanced Perfecting Powder.
I think it's the most powerful powder that gives me a great ceramic skin finish while leaving a semi-matte sheen.
I use this brush and apply it a little bit gently.
I blend the powder with the brush while applying it.
The forehead gets really sweaty, so I think it's okay to use more powder than you think.
When I go to a concert, I use the strongest powder I can find until my forehead is the size of a rice cake, so my skin doesn't break down at all.
I've been using Daifuku, so today's is about semi-matte, so it's about the size of a mandarin orange.
I forgot the most important thing, which is shading.
Shading is so important, but I forget it so easily.
I've never introduced it because it makes me feel different whether I put on shading or not.
I haven't introduced it at all, but this is Cezanne's Shading Stick No. 01.
I'm going to do it more than I thought I would, and then I'm going to blend it with a sponge.
I'll forget about it easily, but I think it's important to have shading.
I love pink so much and I have a lot of pink eye shadows, but I'm going to use pink again today.
I love this Addiction eyeshadow palette so much that I have many more!
May I brag?
I have three base eyeshadow palettes, and I can use any of the three Addiction palettes depending on my mood.
Next, this one.
How can it come off?
This is Boussin Nolan's Petiteur Mini Clutch in No. 400.
These two go well together, so...
First, this color.
This color is a little matte, no lame, so I'm going to use it as a base.
It's a very pretty smoky pink.
It was really hard to get this one.
I'll definitely get what I want, so I'm going to put it on gently.
I put it on as gently as I brush my teeth.
I don't know if I should be as gentle as brushing my teeth.I don't think it's enough to brush your teeth.
Do it as if you were flicking your ears.
If you use a little leftover eyeshadow from your eyelids and do a little work here and there, you can create a gradient.
You can create a gradient by using a little leftover eyeshadow from your eyelids.
You should apply the base eyeshadow until the eyeballs look like eyeballs.
Okay, it's done. Next, I'm going to apply Wivesun Lola here. I'm going to apply Wivesun Lola in this dull pink color to the double width of the eye.
From here, it's like a crescendo.
This side will be darker.
It's so cute!
Very cute, really cute.
This side is thicker and this side is lighter.
When I do makeup, I do it while thinking that it's really cute.
It's important to think that this color is really cute.
Cute! Oh, it's really cute, but...
We're talking about eyeshadow here.
Next, this color? This color, the darker color, from the top of the dark eye to this area.
Use a thin, flat brush like this.
Then, use the remaining dark pink to make the area under the eyes look like a rabbit.
It's done!
Now, I want to put lame on the upper eyelid.
This lamé is amazingly pretty.
Put this on the part of the eyelid where you can feel the eyeballs.
And voila!
So cute! So cute! It's really pretty.
Can you feel it? Can you feel it?
There's some kind of bluish lame in it.
When it's exposed to the sun or light
The sparkle is just amazing.
And if you don't touch it at all, it will go on your tear ducts.
Here's what I use for my tear ducts!
It's Can Make Plump Kohde Eyes No. 01!
This is a special eyeshadow palette for tear troughs!
What?
Not #1, the one I'm using today.
I made a mistake!
I have these two colors.I have these two colors.
I'm going to use No. 02 today.
This one is pinkish.
This one is beige.
First, I'll use the matte color without pearls or anything.
Here it is.
It's really nice! The base for the tear ducts is created.
Then, the color with pearls? The other end, the other side.
A little bit of the other side.
Just a little bit.
Oh...
A little too much? Oh, just a little bit.
It's cute, but then we're going to do the final touch.
I'm going to put on the lamé, which I also used on this eyelid, which I love.
Right here, right here.
Here, just a little bit of this, you know? Just a little bit.
I want it to shine. Eyeshadow.
And now, eyeliner. D-Up eyeliner.
It's called Chiffon Brown. It's a much lighter brown.
I think I can draw on my eyelashes.
I think I can draw it well.
I'm the type of person who draws eyeliner at the corner of my eyes very firmly.
I used to put my life on my eyeliner.
I used to draw it right up to here.
Here.
Here's the mascara. Heroine Make Long & Curl Mascara.
I've been wearing a lash palmer lately.
I've been using it as a base so that it doesn't damage my lashes too much.
I use it as a base, but I don't get dark circles under my eyes at all.
The lashes are done in a way that gives a nice clumpy look.
Move the tip of the mascara
If you want to make a bunch, you can do it vertically like this.
If you want to make a bunch of lashes, you can do it vertically like this, like a wiper.
Try it. Of course.
Of course, the lower lashes are vital, too.
I'm the type of person who concentrates a lot on applying my lashes.I'm the type of person who concentrates a lot when I'm applying lashes.
Don't you concentrate? Eyelashes are the hardest part.
The only time I don't talk is when I'm eating crab.
You know how people don't really talk when they're eating crab?
I've finished the eyelashes.
Don't they look like they can fly?
Next, I would like to go to the eyebrows.
I think the order of eyebrows varies from person to person.
I do my eyelashes first? If I do it after I do my base makeup, it makes my eyelashes too thick.
It makes my eyelashes so much thicker!
It's really surprising, isn't it?
That's why I do my eyebrows after I've done all my eye shadow and eye makeup.
Oh, and I use this for my eyebrows.
This is Sezanne's ultra-fine core eyebrow pencil.
I use 01 light brown.
I love it!
I've been using it for a long time, and I even have a stock of it at home.
The moment I run out, I panic.
I don't have any more, but I don't have any more, so how am I going to draw my eyebrows? What do I do? I'm like, "What am I going to do?
It's so important!
First of all, I start from the end of the eyebrow.
I'm going to fill in what's missing.
We don't do anything unnecessary.
I fill in the missing parts.
I do my own eyebrows.
I shape my eyebrows the way I want them to be.
The eyebrow mascara is Canmake.
Color Change Eyebrow No. 04.
It's really bright and nice!
I have see-through bangs, so depending on the color of my eyebrows
I have see-through bangs, so depending on the color of my eyebrows, it can look like they're already connected.
Sometimes it looks really dark.
So I try to use something as bright as possible, something that doesn't make me look like I'm wearing a lot of hair.
And it's Camake.
Camake is amazing, really.Cammake is amazing, really.
I will do it.
Next time, I'll change the color of my eyebrows.
See you soon.
Is it gone?
More.
Maybe you have very light hair.
But the eyebrows don't seem to disappear at all.
I'm sure there are people out there.
After applying eyebrow mascara
After applying eyebrow mascara, you can remove the presence of eyebrows
I hope you give it a try!
Next, I'm going to do the nose shadow.
I'll show you how to apply nose shadow.
Canmake again!
This is Canmake's shading powder
No. 04.
Use this with a round brush.
This is the bridge of the nose.
This is very important.
And I'm going to put it down here.
Okay.
But, you know, it's important to use the right amount of force.
If you apply it with the wrong amount of force
If you apply it with the wrong amount of force, you'll end up with a really dark color.
And also here, under the nose.
Make it as dark as possible.
Is that the right word?
I'm almost at the end of my makeup.
The last part.
Can you get excited?
It's about time.
Like in a live performance.
I'm going to do the highlights.
Laura Mercier'sLaura Mercier's
Highlighting Powder
Rose Glow.
I'm going to start from this forehead.
I'm going to take it down.
There you go.
Do you see it?
Right here on the top of the lips.
Right here.
See?
It's a little shiny.
I don't want to make it look too shiny.
I want it to look a little shiny.
I'll do that.
The blush is this Dior blush.
Dior Skin Rouge Blush.
Number 212.
It's called Tutu Holographic.
It's really pretty.
It has a little bit of blue in it.
It's pinkish with a hint of blue.
There's a lot of lame in it.
It makes my cheeks shine.
This brush right here...
I got bit by a cherry.
Cherry bit me.
I'm using it.
Around here.
Oh, look.
Look, look.
Right here.
See? This is what I did to make it less transparent.
This is my blush, and I think it's the best course I've taken this year.
Lastly, I put on my lips.
The first thing I use as a moisturizer is this Uliage Moistrip.
I don't use it for color anymore, I use it to moisturize.I don't use this anymore for color or anything, I use it to moisturize.
I'm going to do it.
So for lips, I always use this Kate's Lip Monster.
I think it's pink banana in terms of makeup, so...
I've been using it for a really long time.
I used to eat it when I was a regular on Rabbit Tuesday.
I used to eat a lot of Lip Monster, so I'd put on a lot of Lip Monster.
I'd put on a lot of Lip Monster and then I'd take it off with a tissue.
I'd apply it again, take it off, and go.
But then it didn't come off.
I really trust Lip Monster.
I have so much faith in Lip Monster that I'm going to use it for the rest of my life.
And the name "Lip Monster" is so cute.
"Pink Banana." Wait.
Pink banana?
That's cute.
I thought they were pretty easy to get these days. Tama-chan?
Tamachan?
I want one so bad! I want one too, but I can't afford it.
I just happened to be at the drugstore.
I happened to be at the drugstore when I saw them, so I bought them both for Tamachan.
Where did she go to look? There were quite a few.
And recently, I've been using them too much and they've peeled off a little.
This is a muted sheer tint from Lilimu.
I used a color called Pink Fondue on top to make it a little more luminous.
to make it a little more luminous.
Done!
I didn't forget anything, did I?
She said she didn't.
It's done!
And now the bangs are done, and it's really done!
What do you think?
I'd love to hear what you think,
I would love to hear what you think, and I was only able to do it because you all asked me to do it,
If there is anything you would like me to do, or anything you would like to know, I'm waiting for your comments, so I'd appreciate it!
Please take a look at my daily make-up and if you like it, please refer to it!Please take a look at my daily makeup, if you like!
Thank you for watching today!
Please subscribe to my channel and click the Good button!
Bye bye!